recruitmax.com 2008-06-15

# Vurv Privacy Policy

**Introduction**  
Vurv Technology ("Vurv") takes privacy seriously. In our modern technological world we work to balance the importance of the free flow of information against the importance of an individual's privacy rights.

This Internet Privacy Policy ("Policy") describes the privacy policies applicable to personally identifiable information collected by Vurv, including personally identifiable information collected online at ["http://www.vurv.com](http://www.vurv.com/) (the "Site"). By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this Policy.

**Collection of Personally Identifiable Information**  
Vurv collects personally identifiable information from: (a) individuals who submit information on this Site, (b) employees of our clients; and (c) applicants of our clients (collectively referred to as "Users"). When we use the term "personally identifiable information," we mean any information that can be used to identify a specific individual, such as name, address, telephone number, email address, resume information or birthdate. For example, if you submit a question to us online, we will collect your e-mail address. If you apply for a job with Vurv or if you apply for a job with one of our clients through a client web site, you will be asked to fill out an individual profile. This profile may include your name, postal address, email address, telephone numbers, employment information and other resume information. Users will also be asked to select a username and password. We also collect Users' name, company, industry, postal address, email address and phone number when they register to download research documents and case studies from our Site. Personally identifiable information collected by Vurv may be stored in the United States or any other country in which Vurv or its affiliates, subsidiaries or agents maintain facilities.

**Use of Personally Identifiable Information**  
Vurv uses personally identifiable information to maintain applicant databases and subscription lists, process job applications, complete business transactions, assist customers with compliance obligations, fill and confirm orders for products and services, administer accounts, provide support, and update Vurv's databases. Users may be contacted as necessary for these purposes.

**Disclosure of Personally Identifiable Information**  
Vurv relies on various service providers and other contractors to support its Internet Site and business operations. We may share personally identifiable information collected with these third parties, including without limitation: contractors; web site hosting or information technology consulting services; web site management; marketing and promotion services or partners; data analysis; auditors; lawyers; and other administrative, back-up and security services.

Vurv may also disclose personally identifiable information in order to: (1) comply with applicable laws; (2) respond to governmental inquiries or requests; (3) comply with valid legal process; (4) protect the rights, privacy, safety or property of Vurv, Site visitors, clients or the public; (5) enforce our Terms of Service; and (6) permit us to pursue available remedies or limit the damages that we may sustain.

In the event there is a change in Vurv's corporate structure, including without limitation, merger, consolidation, sale, liquidation or transfer of substantial assets, Vurv may, in its sole and absolute discretion, transfer, sell or assign information collected, including without limitation aggregated information and personally identifiable information, to one or more affiliated or unaffiliated third parties.

**Options to Limit Use of Data**  
We ask Users of this Site to choose whether to receive promotional email updates about products and services offered by Vurv, and we will honor the choices made. If you subsequently decide that you no longer wish to receive promotional emails from Vurv, you may unsubscribe or opt out as described below in the Access and Correction section.

With respect to clients' applicant and employee data, Vurv uses their personally identifiable information solely for the purposes of performing the tasks on behalf of, and under the instruction of, our clients.

**Site Data Collection Practices**  
We collect information about visitors to our Site indirectly through standard web logs, including IP address, what browser is being used, and embedded 3rd party analysis (e.g., Google Analytics) from which a visitor entered the site. Vurv normally uses this information in the aggregate to administer and improve our Site. Aggregate information does not allow us to identify a specific individual. Vurv may collect and analyze aggregate information to determine how many visitors arrived at certain pages of the Site, how long they stayed on those pages, and where they went afterwards. This information allows us to determine which pages might be the most interesting to our visitors and enables us to provide them with a better and richer experience on the Site. Additionally, we may use aggregate information to improve the performance of our Site.

While it is possible that some data may be traceable to an individual, any such linked information will be treated as personally identifiable information for the purposes of this Policy as long as it is so linked.

**Cookies and Pixel Tags**  
Vurv uses "cookies" or similar technologies to store login and general information on visitors' computers. A cookie is a small amount of information that a web site transfers to a computer's hard drive. We use cookies to simplify visitors' access and to tailor our services to visitors' needs and interests. For some services, we offer users the choice of having an ID or password stored in a cookie so that visitors do not need to re-enter it when they return to the Site. No other site can read a cookie set by Vurv, and we cannot read a cookie that another web site wrote to a visitor's computer. Most Internet browsers are set to accept cookies. Users can reset browsers to refuse cookies and still use our Site, although access may be slower and less convenient.

We also may collect data by using "pixel tags," "web beacons," "clear GIFs" or similar means (collectively, "pixel tags") that allow us to know when you visit our Site. Through pixel tags, we do not have access to personal information about you but we obtain aggregate data (i.e., the IP address and the domain name, the areas of the Site you visit, your operating system, your browser version, the URL you came from) which can be used to enhance your online experience.

**Confidentiality & Security Safeguards**  
Vurv takes reasonable technical, administrative and physical steps to protect personally identifiable information collected against unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction. Vurv employees who handle confidential, proprietary, or personally identifiable information are required to treat it confidentially and are not permitted to use it for purposes unrelated to Vurv's business or disclose it to unauthorized third parties. Vurv also requires its third-party service providers to use the personally identifiable information about you solely for the purposes of performing the tasks on behalf of us, and under our instruction.

For online transactions, we use technology to protect the personally identifiable information that you transmit to us via our Site. Unfortunately, however, no security system or system of transmitting data over the Internet can be guaranteed to be entirely secure. If you have reason to believe that your interaction with us is no longer secure, please notify us of the problem by contacting us at [privacy@vurv.com](mailto:privacy@vurv.com).

**External Links**  
This Site may include links to other web sites not controlled by Vurv. Please note that we are not responsible for the collection, use, maintenance, sharing, or disclosure of data and information by such third parties. Once you leave this Site (you can usually tell where you are by checking the URL in the location bar on your browser), use of any information you provide is governed by the privacy policy of the operator of the site you are visiting. That policy may differ from ours. We encourage you to read the privacy policies of web sites that you visit before submitting personal information. If you can't find the privacy policy of any of these web sites via a link from the web site's homepage, you should contact the web site directly for more information.

**Access & Correction**  
In accordance with applicable law, Vurv provides Users with the right to access and correct their personally identifiable information. For information about how to exercise these rights, or to review or change an Internet registration profile, unsubscribe from our newsletters, or to be removed from the Vurv database, please contact Vurv Customer Service, [customerservice@vurv.com](mailto:customerservice@vurv.com). We make reasonable efforts to ensure that the personally identifiable information we have about you is as accurate, current and complete as necessary for the purposes for which we use that data.

**Data from the European Union**  
We comply with the requirements of the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles issued by the U.S. Department of Commerce on July 21, 2000 (the "Safe Harbor Principles") with respect to personally identifiable information received from the European Union. Because we comply with the Safe Harbor Principles, our transfers of such data from countries in the European Union to the United States meet the adequacy requirements of the European Union Data Protection Directive.

**Policy Updates**  
We may update this Policy from time to time. When we do so, changes in our Policy will be effective immediately upon posting the revised policy to the Site. If you are a regular visitor to this Site, we recommend that you check this Policy on a regular basis. You can tell when the policy was last revised by checking the "Last Updated" legend at the top of this page. By continuing to use the Site after a revised policy has been posted, you will be deemed to have agreed to such changes. If you do not agree with the terms of this Policy please do not continue using this Site.

**Contact Information**

Questions regarding this policy should be directed to Vurv at [privacy@vurv.com](mailto:privacy@vurv.com) or by contacting us at: 

Vurv Technology, Inc.  
Attn: Information Security Officer  
7660 Centurion Parkway  
Jacksonville, FL 32256  
USA

**BY USING THIS SITE YOU CONSENT TO THE COLLECTION, USE AND TRANSFER OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION AS DESCRIBED IN THIS POLICY.**
